Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/iggyyuson (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS)
DevOps
Kubernetes

Certifications

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner
AWS Certified Solutions Architect –
Associate
AWS Certified Developer –

Honors-Awards

Associate

1st Place, Computer Programming Contest

Finalist, Science Research Summit

1st Place, Research Fair

1st Place, Research Fair

1st Place, Research Fair

Ike Gabriel Yuson

DevSecOps Engineer | Serverless | AWS User Group Leader Davao del Sur, Davao Region, Philippines

Summary

Iggy is a DevSecOps Engineer with an expertise in implementing cloud-native and serverless applications in AWS. He possesses extensive skills in developing full-stack solutions for both web and mobile platforms.

Outside work, Iggy is also actively volunteering in the local community as the User Group Leader of AWS User Group Davao where he hosts meetups focused on educating and networking among AWS enthusiasts and professionals.

Experience

Ingenuity Software
DevOps Engineer
September 2023 - September 2024 (1 year 1 month)
Davao, Davao Region, Philippines

Elladex

Mid-level Backend Developer April 2022 - March 2024 (2 years) Sydney, New South Wales, Australia

Architected the company's backend infrastructure in AWS. Setup CI/CD in multiple environments and created functional and scalable REST APIs using Node.

Tutorials Dojo Cloud Instructor September 2023 - January 2024 (5 months)

haws

1 year 6 months

Back End Developer
July 2022 - April 2023 (10 months)

Full Stack Developer November 2021 - June 2022 (8 months)

De La Salle University Summer Intern June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months) Metro Manila

Worked closely with data science and machine learning technologies and practiced web scraping using Python.

Education

University of the Philippines

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science

Philippine Science High School Southern Mindanao Campus High School Diploma